blogotechblog.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy

BlogoTech is a Technology & Social Media Blog where we provide valuable content on Social media, Blogging, Android, hacks and a lot more. It is owned by Lalit Indoria who holds responsibility for all the content that is published here on BlogoTech.

## Content

All articles published on BlogoTech are true to the best of out knowledge, however rumors are mentioned in the title. The main aim of this blog is to provide useful information to the world. This blog is also an affiliate of various products which are honestly reviewed by the authors. We do not publish any 18+ content on BlogoTech. If you find something inappropriate on this blog, kindly [let us know](http://www.blogotechblog.com/contact/).

## What Information Do We Collect?

Not much as of now other than your email address (not for spamming you). The email address you enter in the comments form is required but is not used unless you are subscribed to future comments or post or if you get a reply to your comment. We also use your email address when we Give away premium products for free.

Guest authors need to sign up before they submit content. The details you enter in your profile are not used for any purpose except the email address which we use for future communication.

## Ads By Google

BlogoTech is monetized by Google Ads. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. You can view [Privacy Policy for Google Ads and Advertising Services](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html) or [opt out of Google Advertising](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin/) if you do not want Google to track your interests and web activity

## Third Party Advertising

We also serve third party ads apart from Google Ads. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this site. If you wish to opt out of this, kindly [check this](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) to know which companies allow you to opt out of behavioral advertising.

## Third Party Links

We may include links to other websites (including affiliate links) from our content and these websites have their own privacy policy. We are not liable for the content and activity of these sites. We do check  external links and we do not link to any suspicious sites. If you think we do, we would love to get a feedback from you regarding this.

## Damage To Your Possessions

We do not intend to damage your possessions. As already mentioned, the main aim of this Blog is to provide information. We often provide tutorials or hacks where you need to tweak your Computer or any Gadget. We also provide information on rooting Android Devices and jailbreaking your iOS Device which makes your warranty void. We are not responsible for this loss of warranty or any damage that may be caused to your device. However, these tutorials are tested and then published. Follow these tutorials at your own risk.

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We comply with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance) and we do not collect information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our content and services are meant for individuals who are above 13 years of age only.

## Copyright

The content published on BlogoTech is not copied from any site and hence we strictly do not encourage someone copying our content. You can copy a few lines from our content with attribution only. If any copied content is found on any other site, a complaint will be filed with their Advertising partners and the DMCA department of their web hosting company. Kindly do not do this.

## Your Consent

By using this website, you consent to our [website’s privacy policy](http://www.blogotechblog.com/privacy-policy/).

We hold full rights to update our Privacy policy.

This page was last updated on 26th December, 2011
